amazngfacts.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs); to improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) or; to improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
